[{"answer": "She's very, very depressed.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "How would you describe her feelings today?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Absolutely not, no.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Do you get a sense that she knew how disturbed and how depressed her son was?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes, it's completely new because she resides in Brooklyn.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I mean was all this completely knew to his mother?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yes, she was sobbing and she was weeping.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Has she been emotional with you today?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, you let her know that God loves her.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What kind of advice can you give her from a spiritual sense?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes, and the link is probably corded anger.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "The link is the mental illness, isn't it?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Is this -- will you look at what's happened here?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "You know the problem is that, we are not identifying and treating him.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "What is wrong with the way that the criminal and mentally ill paternity of America just not picked up when they're buying these killing machines?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "I mean, Xavier Amador, is that a familiar thing that you hear when people get as Dr. Sophy said to adult age that they can mask these problems of even their closest family?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "You know, I'm here today as Ana's mom.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "What can be done about this, do you think?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I think it might behoove us a nation to put aside bipartisan politics and petty disagreements and agree that no one else wants to be fitting in my shoes right now.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What do you think is the most practically realistic thing that can be achieved given the way the politicians so far completely, in my view, showed any responsibility for this issue?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Of course, she's a victim herself and it's time that in America we start looking at mental illness with compassion and start helping the people who really need it.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Obviously, in your case, Adam Lanza's mother wasn't there to tell that kind of story because she was killed herself, but are you able to feel any sympathy or empathy for people in her position, for the families of these shooters?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I thank his teachers and the staff at Sand Hook Elementary School for saving his life and for making school a safe and fun place.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "How has he been coping and adjusting to life without his sister and also to going back to school?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "You know, right now, I feel better that he is laughing, I feel better that he is enjoying it, and he tells me his favorite subject is lunch.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Would you feel any better if the school that your son was now at had arms guards outside it?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "My daughter loved food, she loved music, and she loved God.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "How would you like her to be remembered?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "My prayer for Congress is to put bickering aside and let's stop arguing about the small thing and let's get to it on the big things.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "What is your message to him and indeed to the members of Congress?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "What I feel is this really disheartening sense of Groundhog Day with these gun massacres and no desire, no strong enough desire by the politicians, all the people of America to do anything constructive about it?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I mean I think you have to have a -- you have to have a mass movement of the people.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Where do we try and get a meeting of minds to get things (inaudible) done so that poor woman who lost her daughter at Sandy Hook can actually see that somebody is reacting to it?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, I'm looking -- I'm concerned about your health.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "But why are you sending me a waistline app?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "No, I think it's both.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Do you feel that these actually have an effect on Americans or do people who watch your documentaries feel horrified and then just carry on (dazzling) them buying more guns?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Relatively normal.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "When you look back over what's happened to you, are you surprise that you've emerged so relatively normal as you appear in the interviews that I've seen?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "As long as I can remember, there was unrest in my father's home.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "At what point did you, yourself then become victim to the abuse?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "When I find out that I was going to be placed by Rulon Jeffs, there was all of these years of everything I've been taught how this was right, this was holy, this was good, and yet inside of me, there was a tremendous amount of disappointment, confusion, and overwhelm.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What is your recollection of the moment that you heard that was what you were going to have to do?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "I mean even at his advanced stage, did you have to perform sexual duties to him, was that part of it?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I was overwhelmed and I was very angry.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "How did you feel emotionally about that?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "They were interesting because, on the outside, they seem to be so kind.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What kind of men were they?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Fortunately, for me, you know, I had actually 64 sister wives and I got along with them all.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What kind of relationship did you have with the other wives?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "The tipping point for me was when Rulon Jeffs died, 56 of his 65 wives were between the age of 17 and 34 and Warren Jeffs was forcing us to be remarried.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "But just going back to the moment that you escaped, what was the tipping point for you and how did you get out of there?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "It was a very emotional time for me.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What were you feeling, were you feeling a great sense of elation when Rulon Jeffs was finally jailed for life or what were you -- what was going to your mind?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I do have two young children.", "docId": "130918pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "And for you, personally, is there marriage on the cards going forward, a real marriage to somebody that you love, children, perhaps?", "qSentId": 534}]